Hercules and the Lost Kingdom is a adventure, fantasy, tv
movie film directed by Harley Cokeliss.
Hercules comes to the aid of a young woman who is seeking the lost city of Troy.
Eventually, Hercules leads her to a camp of refugees from the city,
which has been taken over by Hera's Blue Priests.
Hercules helps the refugees take back the city.
"Hercules and the Lost Kingdom" is the second movie-length pilot episode of
the television series "Hercules: The Legendary Journeys".
Hercules, played by Kevin Sorbo.
Zeus, played by Anthony Quinn.
Deianeira, played by Renée O'Connor.
Waylin, played by Robert Trebor.
Telamon, played by Eric Close.
Queen Omphale, played by Elizabeth Hawthorne.
Hercules and the Lost Kingdom is the second television movie in the
syndicated fantasy series Hercules: The Legendary Journeys.
In the film, Hercules comes to the aid of a young woman
who is seeking the lost city of Troy.
Eventually, Hercules leads her to a camp of refugees from the city,
which has been taken over by Hera's Blue Priests.
Hercules helps the refugees take back the city.
The film explores themes of hero, legend, mythology, greek mythology, god.